Week 13. Day 1. The Wild Amazon. Vine. Moss. Fungi. Tangled. Rainforest. Basin. Species. Discover.
Document. Destruction. Deforestation. Pasture. Accelerate. Remaining. Day 2. A Chinese legend.
Legendary. Taoism. Philosophy. Womb. Biography. Librarian. Contemporary. Confucius.
Pass. Conflicting. Confusion. Collection. Day 3. Whales' silent tears. Population.
Far-reaching. Right. Rarely. Psychological state. Intelligent. Social. Moral. Rescue. Approach.
Thrive. Breeding. Lower. Sonar. Navigate. Day 4. Prehistoric art. Prehistoric. Era. Figurine.
Cave. Etching. Sculpture. Particular. Feature. Detailed. Buffalo. Scene. Up to. Fresh. Meaningful. Day 5.
Rock climbing. Outdoors. Individual. Crawl. Surface. Equipment. Grip. Thrill. Force. Slip.
Intense. Strength. Day 6. The oldest trees in the world. Living. Naturalist. Lifespan. By comparison.
You. Bushe. Cypress. Be named after. Bristlecone. Grove. Twisted. Trunk. Spruce. Spindly. Clonal.
Fairly. Day 7. Headphones and hearing. Headphones. Hearing. Specifically. Earmuffs. Invent. Earbud. Block. Volume. Blast.
Ear canal. Overstressed. Millimeter. Stress. Out. Permanent. Take. For granted.